Predator becomes prey.
Catwoman: Hunted is a animation, action, crime
film directed by Shinsuke Terasawa.
Catwoman's attempt to steal a priceless jewel puts her squarely in the crosshairs of both a powerful
consortium of villains and the ever-resourceful Interpol, not to mention Batwoman.
Selina Kyle / Catwoman (voice), played by Elizabeth Gillies.
Kate Kane / Batwoman (voice), played by Stephanie Beatriz.
Roman Sionis / Black Mask (voice), played by Jonathan Banks.
Solomon Grundy/ Abaddon / Pilot (voice), played by Steve Blum.
Julia Pennyworth (voice), played by Lauren Cohan.
Tobias Whale / Morax (voice), played by Keith David.
Catwoman: Hunted is a 2022 American animated superhero film based on the DC Comics
character Catwoman by Bill Finger and Bob Kane, and produced by Warner Bros.
Animation for DC Entertainment.
It was released on February 8, 2022, by Warner Bros.
Home Entertainment.
It is the 48th installment in the DC Universe Animated Original Movies line.
The film is directed by Shinsuke Terasawa from a script by Greg Weisman.
It stars the voices of Elizabeth Gillies and Stephanie Beatriz.
OLM, a Japanese studio behind the Pokémon anime series, provided their
animation services for the film with their Team Inoue.
The film follows Catwoman as she attempts to steal a priceless jewel, only to get caught in the
crosshairs of a powerful consortium of criminals and villains, the Interpol, and Batwoman.